Lee Hockfield

Supervising Pharmacist - Greater Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company

Warrington, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Lee-Hockfield/f521cfe0a86e777b

Licensed Pharmacist in Pennsylvania, New Jersey and Delaware, with more than 29 years experience in providing superior pharmacy services in retail setting. Compounded medications according to professional standards and practices. Licensed immunizer in Pennsylvania and New Jersey. Highly developed problem solving skills and excellent computer skills. Thorough knowledge of compound drug distribution systems, drug utilization evaluation, emerging medications, inventory management and regulations governing pharmacy services. Seen as an effective liaison between healthcare team and the community to improve drug usage and therapeutic outcomes.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Supervising Pharmacist

Greater Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company - March 1993 to Present

Managed staff of 7 including 2 other pharmacists at fulfilling more than 1000 prescriptions weekly. Consulted with physicians and patients with regard to medication dosage, drug interactions, disease management and potential side effects of prescription and OTC medications. Maintained proper immunization protocols.

Coordinated the activities of pharmacists and technicians in the preparation, labeling and delivery of medications in accordance with physician prescriptions, to ensure compliance with federal, state and local laws and regulations.

Maintained proper inventory levels and minimized out of stock items. Resolved problems with insurance providers concerning billing/reimbursement issues. Improved morale of coworkers leading by example and using humor to diffuse stressful situations.

Supervising Pharmacist

Gene Pharmacy - Abington, PA - October 1991 to March 1993

Staff Pharmacist

Yardley Pharmacy - Yardley, PA - July 1988 to October 1991

Staff Pharmacist

Drug Emporium Pharmacy - Langhorne, PA - May 1987 to July 1988

Staff Pharmacist

CVS Pharmacy - June 1986 to May 1987

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science

Temple University School of Pharmacy May 1986